Male germ cell	CL_0000015	Hermann Steller	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/187
Spermatocyte	CL_0000017	Rudolf Oldenbourg, James R. LaFountain	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/9061
Neuroblast	CL_0000031	Margaret I. Davis	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/14969
Stem cell	CL_0000034	Sabrina Lin, Prue Talbot	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/12625
Hematopoietic stem cell	CL_0000037	Endre Majorovits, Charles Bangham, Stephen Fuller, Mohamed Nejmeddine	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/40120
Neuronal stem cell	CL_0000047	Margaret I. Davis	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible. 	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/14969
Myoblast	CL_0000056	Caroline McKeown	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/1585
Fibroblast	CL_0000057	Klaus Hahn	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/238
Epithelial cell	CL_0000066	Kevin Foskett, Aki yuki Taruno	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/44602
Duct epithelial cell	CL_0000068	Moe Mahjoub, Tim Stearns	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/10060
Blood vessel endothelial cell	CL_0000071	Robert S. Fischer, Clare M. Waterman	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/7330
Barrier epithelial cell	CL_0000073	John E. Michaels, Patricia A. Brown	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/9301
Columnar/cuboidal epithelial cell	CL_0000075	Esther K. Kieserman, Michael Glotzer, John B. Wallingford	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/32023
Squamous epithelial cell	CL_0000076	Graham Wright	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible. 	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/12594
Blood cell	CL_0000081	Jeffrey Skerker, Meg Rush, Roger Wiegand, Tom Morgan	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/27219
T cell	CL_0000084	Endre Majorovits, Charles Bangham, Stephen Fuller, Mohamed Nejmeddine	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/40120
Neuron associated cell	CL_0000095	Andreas Bergmann, Herman Steller	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/217
Mast cell	CL_0000097	Bridget Wilsen	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/222
Sensory epithelial cell	CL_0000098	Kevin Foskett, Aki yuki Taruno	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/44602
Interneuron	CL_0000099	Margaret I. Davis	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/16245
Endothelial cell	CL_0000115	Dee Lauzon, Sue Lancelle, Marian Rice	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/39779
Basket cell	CL_0000118	Margaret I. Davis	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible. 	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/14969
Purkinje cell	CL_0000121	Ronit Ilouz, Varda Lev-Ram, Eric Bushong, Travis Stiles, Dinorah Friedmann-Morvinski, Christopher Douglas, Geoffrey Goldberg, Mark Ellisman, Susan Taylor	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/49451
Glial cell	CL_0000125	NA	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/179
Astrocyte	CL_0000127	Eric A. Bushong, Maryann E. Martone, Mark H. Ellisman	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible. 	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/47033
Oligodendrocyte	CL_0000128	Tomasz Rusielewicz, Carmen Melendez-Vasquez	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/40360
Glandular epithelial cell	CL_0000150	Marian Miller	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/49001
Secretory cell	CL_0000151	Mark Ladinsky, Kathryn E. Howell	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/12925
Parietal cell	CL_0000162	Marian Miller	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/49005
Endocrine cell	CL_0000163	Bridget Wilsen	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/222
Hepatocyte	CL_0000182	Michael Cammer, Phyllis Novikoff	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/34598
Muscle cell	CL_0000187	Hanna Osinska	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/347
Flight muscle cell	CL_0000196	Clara Franzini-Armstrong	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/37398
Taste receptor cell	CL_0000209	Kevin Foskett, Aki yuki Taruno	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/44602
Photoreceptor cell	CL_0000210	Caroline Kizilyaprak, Danièle Spehner, Didier Devys, Patrick Schultz	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/39744
Myelinating schwann cell	CL_0000218	Parysek, Linda	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/247
Ectodermal cell	CL_0000221	Margaret I. Davis	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/14969
Endodermal cell	CL_0000223	Kevin Foskett, Aki yuki Taruno	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/44602
Erythrocyte	CL_0000232	Hans Ris	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://cellimagelibrary.org/images/10088
Macrophage	CL_0000235	Michael Cammer, Dianne Cox	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/35127
Stratified squamous epithelial cell	CL_0000240	Ann Wheeler	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/35619
Keratinocyte	CL_0000312	Ann Wheeler	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/35618
Epidermal cell	CL_0000362	Louisa Howard	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/40388
Plasmatocyte	CL_0000394	Michael Cammer, Phyllis Novikoff	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/35167
Dendritic cell	CL_0000451	Stuart Turville	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/45553
Neuron	CL_0000540	Tina Carvalho	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/214
Lymphocyte	CL_0000542	Endre Majorovits, Charles Bangham, Stephen Fuller, Mohamed Nejmeddine	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/40118
Blood vessel	CL_0000548.2	Edward Harris	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/35464
Orthochromatic erythroblast	CL_0000552	Chris Woodcock	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/700
Reticulocyte	CL_0000558	Woodcock, Chris	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/717
Fat body cell	CL_0000565	Hans Ris	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/24981
Germ cell	CL_0000586	Chris Woodcock, Gayle Miller	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/561
Pyramidal cell	CL_0000598	Margaret I. Davis	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/16243
Muscle precursor cell	CL_0000680	Caroline McKeown	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/1584
Radial glial cell	CL_0000681	Jennifer Bestman	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/26252
Neurecto-epithelial cell	CL_0000710	Esther K. Kieserman, Michael Glotzer, John B. Wallingford	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/32023
Leukocyte	CL_0000738	Endre Majorovits, Charles Bangham, Stephen Fuller, Mohamed Nejmeddine	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/40120
Retinal ganglion cell	CL_0000740	Keun-Young Kim, David Gutmann	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/47051
Cardiac muscle cell	CL_0000746	Dee Lauzon, Sue Lancelle, Marian Rice	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/39754
Erythroblast	CL_0000765	Woodcock, Chris	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/748
Neutrophil	CL_0000775	Mark Harding	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/47307
Thymocyte	CL_0000893	Endre Majorovits, Charles Bangham, Stephen Fuller, Mohamed Nejmeddine	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible. 	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/40118
Pluripotent stem cell	CL_0002248	Abraham Al-Ahmad, Eric Shusta	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/45501
Type II taste cell	CL_0002286	Kevin Foskett, Aki yuki Taruno	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/44602
Embryonic cell	CL_0002321	Margaret I. Davis	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/16245
Embryonic stem cell	CL_0002322	Yuhuan Wang	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/12630
Fibroblast of lung	CL_0002553	Andres J Garcia, Ankur Singh	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/44701
Intestinal epithelial cell	CL_0002563	Lucy O'Brien, David Bilder	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/39686
Schwann cell	CL_0002573	Parysek, Linda	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/247
Retinal progenitor cell	CL_0002672	Caroline Kizilyaprak, Danièle Spehner, Didier Devys, Patrick Schultz	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/39744
Mesenchymal cell	CL_0008019	Louisa Howard	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible.	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/39788
Precursor cell	CL_0011115	Dee Lauzon, Sue Lancelle, Marian Rice	Public Domain: This image is in the public domain and thus free of any copyright restrictions. However, as is the norm in scientific publishing and as a matter of courtesy, any user should credit the content provider for any public or private use of this image whenever possible	http://www.cellimagelibrary.org/images/39756